Guide to the Donald W. Baker College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection, 1950- 1969.
Baker, Donald W. College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection
- Mrs. Vaughn, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00288)
  Description: Mildred Fox, June Vaughn, Florence Grossman, and Marion Ford at a table. June Vaughn is wearing glasses and a dragon fly pin. Published in Ellis Leonard, "Veterinary Centennial in New York State," page 169.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", "2 print on paper (one cropped) 1 print on cardboard (cropped)"
- Unidentified man with child, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00289)
  Description: Unidentified man with a child on his shoulders, holding a piece of chicken
- Drs. Donald O. Taylor, Patricia Corwin Wing and 3 other unidentified members of the Class of 1963, ca. 1963 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00290)
  Description: Drs. Donald O. Taylor (far left), Patricia Corwin Wing and 3 other unidentified members of the Class of 1963, and a puppy
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. Walter R. Krill and K.F. Johnson, 1963 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00291)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Walter R. Krill, Dean of Ohio State Veterinary College, and K.F. Johnson at the 76th annual meeting of the Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9.5", 3 prints on cardboard (2 cropped)
- 1961 JAVMA Picnic, 1961 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00292)
  Description: 1961 JAVMA Picnic, log sawing contest. Peter Olafson looks on with the crowd. See also VPC.00092 and VPC.00085
- 2 unidentified men speaking at the Hotel Hamilton, 1962 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00293)
  Description: Two unidentified men at a podium at the Hotel Hamilton. Notation on original envelope says "printed 12/3/62." See also VPC.00801 and VPC.00298
- Peter Olafson and W.S. Stone, 1965 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00294)
  Description: Candid of Peter Olafson and W. S. Stone and others seated at a banquet in a wallpapered room. Stone is smoking his cigar. Probably an Annual Conference See also VPC.00274, VPC.00300, VPC.00301, VPC.00674 and VPC.00675
- Class of 1963 group posed on a lawn, 1962 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00295)
  Description: Group from Class of 1963 posed on a lawn. Dick Sheehan, class of 1963, is in the back row left with glasses. See also VPC.00047, VPC.00296 and VPC.00297.
- Class of 1963 group posed on a lawn, 1962 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00296)
  Description: Group from Class of 1963 posed on a lawn. Dick Sheehan, class of 1963, is in the back row left with glasses. See also VPC.00047, VPC.00295 and VPC.00297.
- Class of 1963 group posed on a lawn, 1962 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00297)
  Description: Group from Class of 1963 posed on a lawn. Dick Sheehan, class of 1963, is in the back row left with glasses. See also VPC.00047, VPC.00295 and VPC.00296.
- Dr. Karlson at Hotel Hamilton, 1962 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00298)
  Description: Dr. Karlson, from Chicago, at a podium at the Hotel Hamilton. Notation on original envelope says "printed 12/3/62." See also VPC.00801, VPC.00293 and VPC.00427.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "3" x 5" 8" x 10", 3 prints on paper 1 transparency"
- Peter Olafson, and others, 1964 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00299)
  Description: Candid of Peter Olafson, two unidentified men and either Mrs. Larry Conlon or Mrs. J. Lowe. They are seated on one side of a restaurant table. See. Also VPC.00054
- Unidentified men at a banquet., 1965 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00300)
  Description: Unidentified men at a banquet in a wallpapered room. W.S. Scott is one of them. Probably an Annual Conference. See also VPC.00274, VPC.00294, VPC.00301, VPC.00674 and VPC.00675
- Unidentified men at a banquet., 1965 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00301)
  Description: Unidentified men at a banquet in a wallpapered room. W.S. Scott is one of them. Probably an Annual Conference. See also VPC.00274, VPC.00294, VPC.00300, VPC.00674 and VPC.00675
- Unidentified men at a banquet., 1961 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00302)
  Description: Unidentified men at an Annual Conference banquet in a wallpapered room. Ice machine in one corner. Same event is pictured in VPC.00080 and VPC.00707-00710.
- Mrs. Lonnsbury, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00303)
  Description: Candid of Mrs. Lonnsbury, the Dean's Secretary. She holding her hand over the phone receiver. There's a typewriter in the foreground and a dictionary in the background.
- Louise Barr and three unidentified women, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00304)
  Description: Louise Barr and three unidentified women standing in front of a row of cars. Louis is 3rd from left, wearing a plaid shirt.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7" 3" x 5", 2 print on paper
- Gertrude Keenan, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00305)
  Description: Gertrude Keenan, wearing what might be a maternity dress.
- Unidentified man herding cattle, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00306)
  Description: Unidentified man herding cattle thru a chute.
- Cleon Easton with unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00307)
  Description: Candid of Cleon Easton, class of 1951 (with wife?) at a dinner party. She is wearing a sleeveless dress and a pin that matches her earrings.
- Students dissecting an animal, ca. 1960s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00308)
  Description: Students dissecting an animal. 3 are clearly visible in the foreground, crouching or bending over stringy bits of the animal on the floor.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Archie Wilson, Building Engineer, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00309)
  Description: Archie Wilson, first Building Engineer, standing outside one of the old campus buildings. There is a woman on the steps behind him.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5.5" x 9.5", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00310)
  Description: Unidentified man wearing a white shirt, lab coat and tie.. No glasses, smiling, looking right
- Charles R. Omer and Clarence Greenfield Bradt, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00311)
  Description: Candid of Charles R. Omer (Kansas State University Class of 1929) and Clarence Greenfield Bradt at an Annual Conference, possibly the 45th.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "10"" x 10"" 5"" x 10""", 2 prints on paper (one cropped)
- Ralph Knight and A.K. Zellner, 1955 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00312)
  Description: Candid of Ralph Knight, class of 1907, and A. K. Zellner at the 47th Annual Conference
- Grant Kaley, Albert Brown, Aubrey Wooden, Tice, Henry Hodges and unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00313)
  Description: Head table at a dinner party. Pictured are Grant Kaley, Class of 1931; unidentified woman; Albert Brown, Class of 1915; Aubrey Wooden, Class of 1923; (Floyd or Albert?) Tice; and Harry Hodges, Class of 1916.
- S.G. Eddins' practice sign, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00314)
  Description: Sign reading, "S.G. Eddins, D.V.M., Office at Back." The sign belongs to Samuel G. Eddins, Class of 1938.
- Unidentified man and woman, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00315)
  Description: Unidentified man and woman conversing. He is wearing a hat and a trench coat. She has her purse over her arm.
- Mitchell Hutchinson, 1964 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00317)
  Description: Candid of Mitchell Hutchinson at the 56th Annual Conference.
- Unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00318)
  Description: Unidentified older man. He is wearing suit and a diagonally striped tie. He is being patted on the right arm by a hand. He looks like Frank Purdue.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 7.5" x 9", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- A. G. Danks and students, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00319)
  Description: A. G. Danks, class of 1933, wrapping a student's arm in the laboratory. He appears to be illustrating how to wrap a horse's leg. Hind quarter of a horse visible in the foreground.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 8", 1 print on cardboard
- Robert Clark (Box 2, Folder VPC.00320)
  Description: Candid of Robert Clark, class of 1952 seated at a table, holding a cigarette and gesturing.
- Robert Clark, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00321)
  Description: Candid of Robert Clark, class of 1952, smoking a cigarette
- James Belden, 1965 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00322)
  Description: James Belden, class of 1964, with a goat in the lab. There's an unidentified man standing in the background.
  Size and Number of Photographs: " 7.5"" x 9"" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- R. R. Birch, ca. 1940s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00323)
  Description: Formal portrait of R. R. Birch
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 4.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. Delehanty and students, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00324)
  Description: Dr. Delehanty performing surgery on a horse with students observing.
- Grace Kinney Loomis, 1964 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00325)
  Description: Candid of Grace Kinney Loomis, class of 1942 and unidentified woman. Loomis is the older woman on the left. There is a coffee table in the foreground. Loomis's eyes are shut.
- Grace Kinney Loomis, 1964 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00326)
  Description: Candid of Grace Kinney Loomis, class of 1942 and unidentified woman. Loomis is the older woman on the left. There is a coffee table in the foreground
- 4 unidentified students, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00327)
  Description: 4 men examining intestines in a tray in the lab. Student farthest right is black.
- Drs. Sam Guss and Sam Scheidy, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00328)
  Description: Candid of Samuel B. Guss with Samuel F. Scheidy, both of the University of Pennsylvania. One has back turned to the camera.
- Group at a meeting, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00329)
  Description: "6 men at a meeting, ice machine in the background. Left to Right they are: W. C. Reese, class of 1935; Irving Zimmerman, class of 1935; S. M. Krukowski, class of 1935; Albert K. Tice, class of 1935; W. F. Tierney, class of 1935; and C. H. Hoppenstedt, cl"
- Irving Wiswall, ca. 1960s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00330)
  Description: Candid of Irving Wiswall, class of 1954, at a New York State Veterinary Medical Society meeting. There is a rack of pamphlets next to him with "Profitable Management" at the top.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 6" x 8", 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 2 print on paper"
- Dr. Bull and family, 1962 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00331)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Bull and his wife and two of his children. He is partially obscured.
- Dr. Bull and family, 1962 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00332)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Bull and his wife and three children. One of them is holding cotton candy.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7.5"" x 8.5"" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- R. W. Kirk and A. Lavignette, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00333)
  Description: Conference TV demonstration by R. W. Kirk and A. Lavignette. Kirk is standing next to a graph entitled "Normal Electrocardiograph." An unconscious dog is visible in the foreground.
- Class in restraint, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00334)
  Description: A group of students watching 4 other students restrain a horse on a lawn at old campus.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. Wendell Moore and family, 1963 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00335)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Wendell Moore, Class of 1963, with wife and daughter at Commencement,
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 5" x 7", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Edgar W. Tucker and his wife, 1964 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00336)
  Description: Edgar W. (Brud) Tucker and his wife at a dinner table at a conference. A black waiter is behind them.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 3" x 5", 1 print on paper, 2 prints on cardboard"
- Edgar W. (Brud) Tucker and his wife, 1964 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00337)
  Description: Edgar W. (Brud) Tucker and his wife at a dinner table at a conference. Dr. Tuckeris looking up at the camera.
- Harold Nadler and Duncan, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00338)
  Description: Candid of Harold Nadler, Class of 1939, and Duncan sitting at a table. Duncan is young, blond and has his hands clasped on the table. He is not looking at the camera
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 4"" x 7.5""", 2 prints on cardboard (one cropped)
- Roland Whitehead, 1964 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00339)
  Description: Candid of Roland Whitehead, class of 1944. He has a flat top, and appears to be in a kitchen. In the full print, there is an unidentified couple standing next to him.
- Drs. Hoppenstedt and Fincher, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00341)
  Description: Candid of Clifford Henry Hoppenstedt, Class of 1935, and Myron Fincher at a conference talking to an unidentified man
- Drs. William Davidson and Arthur Davidson, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00342)
  Description: Candid of William Davidson, class of 1952 and Arthur Calwell Davidson, Class of 1926. The elder Davidson is holding a card in his hand. Both are looking at the camera.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "11"" x 14"" 8" x 10", 2 prints on paper (1 cropped)
- Dr. K. Das and 2 unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00343)
  Description: Dr. K. Das on the left, with 2 unidentified men. They are reading a piece of paper. There is a round table in the foreground with two ashtrays and some papers on it. There are double doors in the background.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man, woman and child, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00344)
  Description: Unidentified man and woman and child. The girl is standing on a table between them.
- H. C. Stephenson and John Kingsbury, ca. 1960s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00345)
  Description: Candid of Hadley C. Stephenson, Class of 1920, and John Kingsbury, Cornell professor of plant biology. They are outside of the Schurman Hall parking lot. Same event is pictured in VPC.00685.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "4.5"" x 7.5"" (cropped) 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 2 prints on paper"
- Fred Hoyt, Class of 1933, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00346)
  Description: Fred Hoyt, Class of 1933. There is a sign behind him advertising Cornell's Lynah Ice Rink
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7" 8" x 10", 4 prints on paper
- Donald Dean, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00347)
  Description: Candid of Donald Dean, class of 1941, sitting at a table with a pencil and what might be a conference program. He is wearing a bow tie and glasses.
- Unidentified woman and Mrs. Burda, 1963 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00348)
  Description: Candid of unidentified woman and Mrs. Burda. One is wearing a lab coat, the other has a sweater with a lace collar. There is a man at a microscope in the background.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 3" x 5", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified man and woman, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00349)
  Description: Unidentified man and woman seated in chairs, possibly Dr. and Mrs. Skinner. He is wearing a bow tie. There is an end table with a lamp between them.
- Dr. and Mrs. M. F. Mather, 1963 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00350)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. M. Foster Mather, Class of 1963, at Commencement. He is in cap and gown.
- Aubry Wooden, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00351)
  Description: Candid of Aubry Wooden, Class of 1923, looking through a microscope, sitting sideways on a chair.
- John Minster, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00353)
  Description: Candid of John Minster, class of 1932. He is wearing a suit and tie. The tie has a diamond pattern.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 10.5", 1 print on paper
- Howard K. Fuller carrying a milk pail, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00354)
  Description: Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, class of 1932, outside carrying a milk pail. He is wearing a wool jacket and cap.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 1 print on particle board
- Hugh Mouat and George E. McConnell, 1955 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00355)
  Description: Hugh Mouat, class of 1929, and George. E. McConnell, class of 1929, at the 47th Annual Conference. The unidentified man is wearing a flowered tie.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9", 1 print on particle board
- Drs Howard, Murray, Fuller and unidentified man, ca. 1940s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00356)
  Description: 4 men sitting on a wall outside. Left to right they are: unidentified man; Howard, class of 1932; Murray, class of 1934; and Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, class of 1932.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 8.5", 1 print on particle board
- Drs. Fortune and Wohnsiedler, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00357)
  Description: Richard L. Fortune, class of 1935 and George Wohnsiedler, class of 193. They are sitting in chairs with legs crossed. Wohnsiedler has a pipe.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 8.5", 1 print on paper
- W.R. Woolridge, 1956 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00358)
  Description: W.R. Woolridge (Animal Trust London) holding his glasses. See also VPC.00398 and VPC.00399.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 10", 2 prints on paper
- Unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00359)
  Description: Unidentified dark haired woman wearing a skirt and matching jacket with round wooden buttons. She is biting her lower lip.
- Couple dancing, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00360)
  Description: Unidentified young couple dancing. She has her back to the camera. He has a flower in his lapel.
- Joseph Dufresne, 1960 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00361)
  Description: Candid of Joseph Dufresne, class of 1936. Dean of School of Veterinary Medicine, St. Hyacinthe, Quebec. He has a mustache and looks like a young Walter Cronkite
  Size and Number of Photographs: "8"" x 9.5"" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Francis Reed, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00362)
  Description: Candid of Francis Irving Reed, class of 1926
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 8.5", 9" x 10", 8.5" x 11", 3 prints on paper
- Gordon Darby and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00363)
  Description: Candid of unidentified man and R. N. Gordon Darby. Darby is in a button down shirt and a hat, the other in his coveralls
- Annual Conference Attendees, ca. 1950s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00364)
  Description: "Posed shot of 7 Annual Conference attendees. Left to right are: Seth Johnson, class of 1929; Holden, Charles Morris, class of 1917; Frank S. Graziadei, class of 1929; G. E. McConnell, class of 1929; unidentified man; and Jean Smith, Class of 1929. See "
  Size and Number of Photographs: "7"" x 9.5"" 4"" x 7"" 4.5" x 6"", "1 print on particle board 2 prints on cardboard (cropped)"
- Annual Conference Attendees, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00365)
  Description: Posed shot of eight Annual Conference attendees. Left to right are: Seth Johnson, class of 1929; Holden; Donald W. Baker, class of 1929; Frank S. Graziadei, class of 1929; Charles Morris, class of 1917; unidentified man; G. E. McConnell, class of 1929
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 8", 2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Students dissecting a horse, ca. 1965 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00366)
  Description: 8 students dissecting a horse. Victor Sancho, Class of 1966, may be one of the students (according to Leonard's Baker list). See also VPC.00367 and VPC.00368
- Students dissecting a horse, ca. 1965 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00367)
  Description: 8 students dissecting a horse. Victor Sancho, Class of 1966, may be one of the students (according to Leonard's Baker list). See also VPC.00366 and VPC.00368
- Students dissecting a horse, ca. 1965 (Box 5b, Folder VPC.00368)
  Description: 8 students dissecting a horse. Victor Sancho, Class of 1966, may be one of the students (according to Leonard's Baker list). See also VPC.00366 and VPC.00367
- Dr. Santoro and Louise Barr, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00369)
  Description: Dr. Santoro and Louise Barr in the lab
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 6.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Francis Fox as Santa, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00370)
  Description: Francis Fox dressed as Santa, reading a list of who's naughty and nice. See also VPC.00373.
- Francis Fox and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00371)
  Description: Francis Fox and unidentified man standing outside in winter. Fox is petting a dog and wearing sunglasses. Looks like an ambulatory call.
- Francis Fox as Santa, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00372)
  Description: Francis Fox as Santa, carrying a sack and a bell. Pine cones in foreground
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on particle board"
- Francis Fox as Santa, ca. 1950s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00373)
  Description: Francis Fox dressed as Santa, reading a list of who's naughty and nice. See also VPC.00370
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 8.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Francis Fox and Eugene Layton, 1965 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00374)
  Description: Francis Fox and Eugene Layton, both with cigars. Clock says 4:30. See also VPC.00272.
- Meyers and Fox and others, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00375)
  Description: Men at a restaurant table, including Francis Fox, class of 1945, and someone Ellis Leonard identified as "Meyers, class of 1952."
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 1 print on particle board
- Francis Fox and P.P. Levine, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00376)
  Description: Francis Fox and P.P Levine standing outside Schurman Hall.
- Francis Fox, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00377)
  Description: Francis Fox laughing with his eyes shut.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "2"" x 3"" 3"" x 5.5""", 2 prints on paper
- Francis Fox, Les Wagers, and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00378)
  Description: Francis Fox, Les Wagers, and unidentified man sitting in a dining room. Fox has his legs crossed so that the embroidered "F" on his sock is visible.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 10", 2 prints on paper (one cropped)
- Faculty at a Senior Picnic, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00379)
  Description: Faculty at a Senior Picnic. The five men are seated at a picnic table. Pictured are: Alexander Zeissig, Edward Melby, Robert Squire, Francis Fox, and Karol Reinhardt
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9"x 6.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Drs. Stevens, Fox and Miller, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00380)
  Description: [left to right] Guy Gross Stevens, Class of 1911, Francis H. Fox, Class of 1945, and Albert W. Miller, Class of 1949. Fox is standing and speaking. See also VPC.00381, VPC.00441 and VPC.00679-00683 for what appears to be the same event.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 10" x 10", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Drs. Miller, Baker and McEntee, ca. 1960s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00381)
  Description: [left to right] Albert W. Miller, Class of 1949, De Witt T. Baker, Class of 1944, and Kenneth McEntee, Class of 1944. Baker is standing and speaking. See also VPC.00380, VPC.00441 and VPC.00679-00683 for what appears to be the same event.
- Barnes, Hagan and Shahan, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00382)
  Description: Left to right, Barnes, William A Hagan and Maurice Shahan. Portraits of James Law, Veranus Moore and Pierre Fish are hanging on the wall behind them.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" (one cropped) 7"" x 8"" (cropped)", 3 prints on cardboard (two cropped)
- William A. Hagan sitting on the edge of a table, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00383)
  Description: Candid of Dean Hagan, sitting on the edge of a table holding his glasses.
- William Hagan and W.O. Kester, ca. 1950s (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00384)
  Description: Candid of William A Hagan and W.O Kester. Kester is in uniform.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 9", 1 print on particle board
- W.S. Stone, Denny Udall, Mrs. Sunderville and W.A. Hagan, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00385)
  Description: W.S. Stone, Denny Hammond Udall, Mrs. Sunderland, and William A. Hagan seated on couch.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 7.5", 1 print on particle board